letterrep.com 2007-10-11

# Privacy Page - We care about your privacy.

Depending on what you do when you visit any web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site's owners. This includes LetterRep.com. We value privacy and think you do too, so we want you to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any web site, we think it's a good idea for you to first understand what that site's privacy policies are. If the site doesn't tell you, don't hesitate to ask. At www.LetterRep.com and its related sites (collectively "LetterRep.com"), we use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make LetterRep.com as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services.  _**LetterRep.com will never sell your private information to any third party.   LetterRep.com will, however, comply with all requests for information from law enforcement agencies, subpoenas, court orders, or similar requests or orders.**_

**_Browsing:_**  
We use standard web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit LetterRep.com, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors.

**_Notice:_**  
"Personal information" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address. While you can browse our site without providing any personal information, you will need to provide some personal information in order to take advantage of certain features.

**_Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services:_**  
For some of the features of our site, you will be asked to provide your personal information. If you request a letter from us, LetterRep.com will use your e-mail address to reply to you with the letter. If you sign up for the on-line course, your e-mail address will be used for sending you editions. We do not sell personal information of our visitors. 

**_Membership:_**

**Paid Subscription Membership** \- Paid subscription members are required to enter their personal information and make payment through the e-commerce gateway. Paid subscription memberships are for a 30, 90 or 365 day period. 

**_Posting Private_ **_**Information** – One of the benefits of membership in LetterRep.com is the ability to request custom letters.  These letters are designed by our writers to meet your specific needs.  When you request a custom letter, you will be asked to describe the letter and what you want the letter to achieve.  Be aware that this information will be posted for all of our writers to review.  LetterRep.com does not screen this information for you.  It is up to you to take care not to reveal any personal information, or information that is private, confidential, or potentially embarrassing._    

**_Letters and Letter Templates_** _  – In the process of composing letters for requestors, LetterRep.com uses the information provided by requestors for the content of the letter.  While in some cases the request and its pertinent information are general in nature and allow for letters to be composed in a template format, due to the level of detail of some requests and the necessity to write the letter in such a way as to meet the requestor's needs, many letters cannot be composed as templates.  These letters will be written to the requestor's specifications and will be posted to the site.  No letters will be removed from the site after they have been posted._

**_Linking To Other Sites:_**  
Please remember that when you use a link to go from LetterRep.com to another web site, the LetterRep.com Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including any site that has a link on LetterRep.com, is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**_Changes to the LetterRep.com Privacy Policy:_**  
This Privacy Policy was updated in August 2006. LetterRep.com reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. LetterRep.com takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. LetterRep.com will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. _You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates_.

**_How to contact LetterRep.com:_**  
Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any LetterRep.com related services, you consent to LetterRep's processing of this information in the United States as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about LetterRep.com's privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to _e-mail us_.
